[
  {
    "question": "c^2 - 4c - 5",
    "answer": "(c + 1)(c - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 - 9",
    "answer": "(c + 3)(c - 3)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 - 9c + 20",
    "answer": "(c - 5)(c - 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "q^2 + 5q + 6",
    "answer": "(q + 3)(q + 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "p^2 - 2p - 15",
    "answer": "(p + 3)(p - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "n^2 + n - 6",
    "answer": "(n + 3)(n - 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + 7a + 12",
    "answer": "(a + 3)(a + 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + 8a + 16",
    "answer": "(a + 4)(a + 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "q^2 - 10q + 25",
    "answer": "(q - 5)(q - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 - 2a - 8",
    "answer": "(a + 2)(a - 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 - 3c - 10",
    "answer": "(c + 2)(c - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "p^2 + 3p - 4",
    "answer": "(p - 1)(p + 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 + 9b + 20",
    "answer": "(b + 4)(b + 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 - 2a - 8",
    "answer": "(a - 4)(a + 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "p^2 - 2p - 3",
    "answer": "(p - 3)(p + 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + 2a - 3",
    "answer": "(a + 3)(a - 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 - 16",
    "answer": "(b - 4)(b + 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 - 7a + 10",
    "answer": "(a - 5)(a - 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "m^2 - 16",
    "answer": "(m + 4)(m - 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "m^2 - 3m - 4",
    "answer": "(m + 1)(m - 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 + 4c + 4",
    "answer": "(c + 2)(c + 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "p^2 + 4p + 3",
    "answer": "(p + 1)(p + 3)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 - 4b + 3",
    "answer": "(b - 3)(b - 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 - 4c - 5",
    "answer": "(c - 5)(c + 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + 4a - 5",
    "answer": "(a + 5)(a - 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 - 4c + 3",
    "answer": "(c - 3)(c - 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "q^2 - 6q + 9",
    "answer": "(q - 3)(q - 3)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 + 2c - 8",
    "answer": "(c + 4)(c - 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "n^2 + n - 2",
    "answer": "(n + 2)(n - 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 - 3c - 10",
    "answer": "(c + 2)(c - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "n^2 + 4n - 5",
    "answer": "(n + 5)(n - 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "q^2 - 2q - 8",
    "answer": "(q - 4)(q + 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + a - 12",
    "answer": "(a - 3)(a + 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + 4a + 3",
    "answer": "(a + 3)(a + 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + 3a - 4",
    "answer": "(a - 1)(a + 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + 9a + 20",
    "answer": "(a + 4)(a + 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "n^2 - 7n + 10",
    "answer": "(n - 5)(n - 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 + 5c + 4",
    "answer": "(c + 4)(c + 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 - 5b + 6",
    "answer": "(b - 3)(b - 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "n^2 - 25",
    "answer": "(n + 5)(n - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 + 6b + 5",
    "answer": "(b + 5)(b + 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 - 4a + 3",
    "answer": "(a - 3)(a - 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 + 10c + 25",
    "answer": "(c + 5)(c + 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "n^2 - 6n + 5",
    "answer": "(n - 1)(n - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 - 6c + 5",
    "answer": "(c - 5)(c - 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 + 4c - 5",
    "answer": "(c - 1)(c + 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "p^2 - 7p + 12",
    "answer": "(p - 3)(p - 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "m^2 - m - 20",
    "answer": "(m - 5)(m + 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "x^2 - 9",
    "answer": "(x - 3)(x + 3)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 + 6c + 8",
    "answer": "(c + 2)(c + 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 - 7bp + 12p^2",
    "answer": "(b - 4p)(b - 3p)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 + 2cz - 15z^2",
    "answer": "(c - 3z)(c + 5z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "p^2 + 2py - 8y^2",
    "answer": "(p + 4y)(p - 2y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "q^2 - 6qx + 5x^2",
    "answer": "(q - x)(q - 5x)"
  },
  {
    "question": "n^2 + 3ny - 10y^2",
    "answer": "(n - 2y)(n + 5y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "m^2 + 10mq + 25q^2",
    "answer": "(m + 5q)(m + 5q)"
  },
  {
    "question": "p^2 + 2px - 3x^2",
    "answer": "(p - x)(p + 3x)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 - 2bq - 3q^2",
    "answer": "(b + q)(b - 3q)"
  },
  {
    "question": "m^2 + 2mq - 3q^2",
    "answer": "(m + 3q)(m - q)"
  },
  {
    "question": "n^2 + 8nx + 15x^2",
    "answer": "(n + 5x)(n + 3x)"
  },
  {
    "question": "n^2 - 8nq + 15q^2",
    "answer": "(n - 3q)(n - 5q)"
  },
  {
    "question": "q^2 + qy - 12y^2",
    "answer": "(q + 4y)(q - 3y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "n^2 + 8np + 15p^2",
    "answer": "(n + 5p)(n + 3p)"
  },
  {
    "question": "q^2 - 4qz + 3z^2",
    "answer": "(q - z)(q - 3z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 + 6bp + 8p^2",
    "answer": "(b + 4p)(b + 2p)"
  },
  {
    "question": "p^2 + 7px + 10x^2",
    "answer": "(p + 2x)(p + 5x)"
  },
  {
    "question": "x^2 - xz - 6z^2",
    "answer": "(x + 2z)(x - 3z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "x^2 - 4y^2",
    "answer": "(x + 2y)(x - 2y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 + 6bc + 5c^2",
    "answer": "(b + c)(b + 5c)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + 3ap + 2p^2",
    "answer": "(a + 2p)(a + p)"
  },
  {
    "question": "m^2 + 2mz - 15z^2",
    "answer": "(m - 3z)(m + 5z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + 3aq - 10q^2",
    "answer": "(a - 2q)(a + 5q)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 - 5by + 4y^2",
    "answer": "(b - 4y)(b - y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 - 2aq - 3q^2",
    "answer": "(a - 3q)(a + q)"
  },
  {
    "question": "p^2 + px - 6x^2",
    "answer": "(p - 2x)(p + 3x)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 - 10bm + 25m^2",
    "answer": "(b - 5m)(b - 5m)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 + bx - 2x^2",
    "answer": "(b - x)(b + 2x)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 + cn - 20n^2",
    "answer": "(c + 5n)(c - 4n)"
  },
  {
    "question": "n^2 - 2np + p^2",
    "answer": "(n - p)(n - p)"
  },
  {
    "question": "n^2 + 7nq + 10q^2",
    "answer": "(n + 5q)(n + 2q)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 - 10bm + 25m^2",
    "answer": "(b - 5m)(b - 5m)"
  },
  {
    "question": "q^2 - qy - 20y^2",
    "answer": "(q + 4y)(q - 5y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 - 10ap + 25p^2",
    "answer": "(a - 5p)(a - 5p)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 - 3ac - 10c^2",
    "answer": "(a + 2c)(a - 5c)"
  },
  {
    "question": "y^2 + 6yz + 8z^2",
    "answer": "(y + 4z)(y + 2z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 + 2bn - 3n^2",
    "answer": "(b - n)(b + 3n)"
  },
  {
    "question": "q^2 - 9qy + 20y^2",
    "answer": "(q - 4y)(q - 5y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 - bp - 20p^2",
    "answer": "(b - 5p)(b + 4p)"
  },
  {
    "question": "q^2 - 2qy - 3y^2",
    "answer": "(q - 3y)(q + y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "n^2 - 10np + 25p^2",
    "answer": "(n - 5p)(n - 5p)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + 8ay + 16y^2",
    "answer": "(a + 4y)(a + 4y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + 3aq - 4q^2",
    "answer": "(a - q)(a + 4q)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 + 2by - 8y^2",
    "answer": "(b + 4y)(b - 2y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 + 5cm + 4m^2",
    "answer": "(c + m)(c + 4m)"
  },
  {
    "question": "p^2 - 6py + 9y^2",
    "answer": "(p - 3y)(p - 3y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "y^2 + 7yz + 10z^2",
    "answer": "(y + 2z)(y + 5z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + aq - 2q^2",
    "answer": "(a + 2q)(a - q)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 - bz - 2z^2",
    "answer": "(b + z)(b - 2z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 + 5cq + 6q^2",
    "answer": "(c + 3q)(c + 2q)"
  },
  {
    "question": "c^2 - 6cn + 5n^2",
    "answer": "(c - n)(c - 5n)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2n^2 - 11n + 12",
    "answer": "(2n - 3)(n - 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "9a^2 - 25",
    "answer": "(3a - 5)(3a + 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6b^2 + 17b + 12",
    "answer": "(3b + 4)(2b + 3)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6q^2 - 25q + 25",
    "answer": "(3q - 5)(2q - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2a^2 + 15a + 25",
    "answer": "(a + 5)(2a + 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "3b^2 - 13b + 4",
    "answer": "(b - 4)(3b - 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "m^2 + 5m + 4",
    "answer": "(m + 4)(m + 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6m^2 + 13m + 5",
    "answer": "(3m + 5)(2m + 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x^2 - 11x + 4",
    "answer": "(3x - 4)(2x - 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2a^2 + 3a + 1",
    "answer": "(a + 1)(2a + 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6m^2 - 19m + 10",
    "answer": "(2m - 5)(3m - 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "9m^2 - 6m - 8",
    "answer": "(3m - 4)(3m + 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x^2 - 11x - 10",
    "answer": "(2x - 5)(3x + 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "n^2 - n - 6",
    "answer": "(n + 2)(n - 3)"
  },
  {
    "question": "b^2 + 7b + 10",
    "answer": "(b + 5)(b + 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6n^2 + 7n - 20",
    "answer": "(2n + 5)(3n - 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "3b^2 + 4b - 4",
    "answer": "(3b - 2)(b + 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "3n^2 + 8n - 16",
    "answer": "(3n - 4)(n + 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6b^2 + 25b + 25",
    "answer": "(2b + 5)(3b + 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6c^2 - 25c + 25",
    "answer": "(2c - 5)(3c - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6b^2 - 13b + 5",
    "answer": "(2b - 1)(3b - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "3a^2 + 4a - 15",
    "answer": "(3a - 5)(a + 3)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2m^2 - 5m - 25",
    "answer": "(m - 5)(2m + 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "9b^2 + 9b - 10",
    "answer": "(3b + 5)(3b - 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "4a^2 - 20a + 25",
    "answer": "(2a - 5)(2a - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6p^2 + 19p + 15",
    "answer": "(2p + 3)(3p + 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "3n^2 + 17n + 20",
    "answer": "(n + 4)(3n + 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2m^2 - 11m + 12",
    "answer": "(2m - 3)(m - 4)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2m^2 - 5m + 3",
    "answer": "(2m - 3)(m - 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "4c^2 + 20c + 25",
    "answer": "(2c + 5)(2c + 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "9m^2 + 6m - 8",
    "answer": "(3m + 4)(3m - 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2m^2 - 7m + 6",
    "answer": "(2m - 3)(m - 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2m^2 - 9m + 9",
    "answer": "(2m - 3)(m - 3)"
  },
  {
    "question": "4a^2 + 12a + 5",
    "answer": "(2a + 5)(2a + 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "9x^2 - 3x - 2",
    "answer": "(3x + 1)(3x - 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6b^2 - 19b + 10",
    "answer": "(3b - 2)(2b - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "9a^2 + 9a + 2",
    "answer": "(3a + 1)(3a + 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2x^2 + 3x - 20",
    "answer": "(x + 4)(2x - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "3p^2 - 2p - 8",
    "answer": "(3p + 4)(p - 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2n^2 + n - 6",
    "answer": "(2n - 3)(n + 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2n^2 + 5n + 2",
    "answer": "(2n + 1)(n + 2)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6b^2 + 13b + 6",
    "answer": "(3b + 2)(2b + 3)"
  },
  {
    "question": "4c^2 - 12c + 9",
    "answer": "(2c - 3)(2c - 3)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6b^2 - 17b + 5",
    "answer": "(3b - 1)(2b - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "4b^2 - 16b + 15",
    "answer": "(2b - 3)(2b - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6b^2 + 5b + 1",
    "answer": "(3b + 1)(2b + 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "4m^2 + 8m + 3",
    "answer": "(2m + 1)(2m + 3)"
  },
  {
    "question": "p^2 + 7p + 12",
    "answer": "(p + 4)(p + 3)"
  },
  {
    "question": "9a^2 - 3a - 20",
    "answer": "(3a + 4)(3a - 5)"
  },
  {
    "question": "9y^2 + 9y + 2",
    "answer": "(3y + 2)(3y + 1)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6a^2 + 19ax + 10x^2",
    "answer": "(2a + 5x)(3a + 2x)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6n^2 + 11nz + 3z^2",
    "answer": "(3n + z)(2n + 3z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6c^2 + cx - 15x^2",
    "answer": "(3c + 5x)(2c - 3x)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6n^2 + 17nq + 5q^2",
    "answer": "(3n + q)(2n + 5q)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6b^2 - 13bz - 5z^2",
    "answer": "(2b - 5z)(3b + z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6n^2 - 11nx - 10x^2",
    "answer": "(3n + 2x)(2n - 5x)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2a^2 + 3ay - 2y^2",
    "answer": "(a + 2y)(2a - y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6n^2 - nx - x^2",
    "answer": "(2n - x)(3n + x)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6b^2 - 17bz + 5z^2",
    "answer": "(2b - 5z)(3b - z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2c^2 - 5cy - 25y^2",
    "answer": "(c - 5y)(2c + 5y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "9b^2 - 9bm - 10m^2",
    "answer": "(3b + 2m)(3b - 5m)"
  },
  {
    "question": "3m^2 + 8mz - 16z^2",
    "answer": "(3m - 4z)(m + 4z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6m^2 + 5mx - 4x^2",
    "answer": "(3m + 4x)(2m - x)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2m^2 - 3mx - 20x^2",
    "answer": "(m - 4x)(2m + 5x)"
  },
  {
    "question": "4n^2 - 9p^2",
    "answer": "(2n - 3p)(2n + 3p)"
  },
  {
    "question": "4b^2 + 20bc + 25c^2",
    "answer": "(2b + 5c)(2b + 5c)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2b^2 - 13bq + 15q^2",
    "answer": "(2b - 3q)(b - 5q)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6m^2 - 17mz + 5z^2",
    "answer": "(3m - z)(2m - 5z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "4b^2 + 12bc + 5c^2",
    "answer": "(2b + c)(2b + 5c)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x^2 + 7xz - 3z^2",
    "answer": "(2x + 3z)(3x - z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6p^2 + 17pz + 12z^2",
    "answer": "(2p + 3z)(3p + 4z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "9c^2 + 9cn + 2n^2",
    "answer": "(3c + n)(3c + 2n)"
  },
  {
    "question": "3q^2 + 17qy + 20y^2",
    "answer": "(3q + 5y)(q + 4y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2b^2 + 5bx - 3x^2",
    "answer": "(b + 3x)(2b - x)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2m^2 - 15mz + 25z^2",
    "answer": "(2m - 5z)(m - 5z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "9n^2 - 16y^2",
    "answer": "(3n + 4y)(3n - 4y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "4n^2 - 8nx - 5x^2",
    "answer": "(2n + x)(2n - 5x)"
  },
  {
    "question": "4n^2 + 12nq + 5q^2",
    "answer": "(2n + 5q)(2n + q)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6n^2 + 11nq + 4q^2",
    "answer": "(2n + q)(3n + 4q)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6m^2 + my - 15y^2",
    "answer": "(3m + 5y)(2m - 3y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "4c^2 - 8cn + 3n^2",
    "answer": "(2c - 3n)(2c - n)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2b^2 + 9bz - 5z^2",
    "answer": "(2b - z)(b + 5z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "4c^2 - n^2",
    "answer": "(2c + n)(2c - n)"
  },
  {
    "question": "4m^2 + 8my - 5y^2",
    "answer": "(2m - y)(2m + 5y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6m^2 - my - 12y^2",
    "answer": "(3m + 4y)(2m - 3y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "9n^2 + 12nz - 5z^2",
    "answer": "(3n + 5z)(3n - z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2p^2 + 9py + 10y^2",
    "answer": "(2p + 5y)(p + 2y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + 6ab + 5b^2",
    "answer": "(a + 5b)(a + b)"
  },
  {
    "question": "9m^2 - 9mz - 4z^2",
    "answer": "(3m + z)(3m - 4z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6m^2 - my - 2y^2",
    "answer": "(3m - 2y)(2m + y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6a^2 - 13az + 6z^2",
    "answer": "(2a - 3z)(3a - 2z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x^2 - 11xz + 10z^2",
    "answer": "(3x - 5z)(x - 2z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "9m^2 - 16y^2",
    "answer": "(3m - 4y)(3m + 4y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6a^2 - 17an + 12n^2",
    "answer": "(2a - 3n)(3a - 4n)"
  },
  {
    "question": "4c^2 - 4cm - 3m^2",
    "answer": "(2c + m)(2c - 3m)"
  },
  {
    "question": "2b^2 + by - 15y^2",
    "answer": "(2b - 5y)(b + 3y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "n^2 - 25x^2",
    "answer": "(n + 5x)(n - 5x)"
  },
  {
    "question": "3x^2 + 5xz - 2z^2",
    "answer": "(3x - z)(x + 2z)"
  },
  {
    "question": "a^2 + 8ay + 15y^2",
    "answer": "(a + 3y)(a + 5y)"
  },
  {
    "question": "6x^2 + 19xz + 15z^2",
    "answer": "(3x + 5z)(2x + 3z)"
  }
]